The Buckingham Murders is a crime, mystery,
thriller film directed by Hansal Mehta.
Fresh wounds are reopened when Jasmeet Bhamra, a cop and a single mother who recently lost her child in
a shooting spree, transfers to High Wycombe and is assigned a case of a missing child.
DS Jaspreet 'Jazz' Bhamra, played by Kareena Kapoor Khan.
Daljeet Kohli, played by Ranveer Brar.
Miller, played by Keith Allen.
DI Hardik 'Hardy' Patel, played by Ash Tandon.
Preeti Sethi, played by Prabhleen Sandhu.
Indrani Rai, played by Sarah-Jane Dias.
The Buckingham Murders is a 2023 Indian crime thriller film directed by Hansal Mehta and starring Kareena Kapoor Khan
as a grieving British-Indian detective who is assigned the case of a murdered child in Buckinghamshire.
It is written by Aseem Arrora, Raghav Raj Kakker, and Kashyap Kapoor and
produced by Kareena Kapoor Khan, Shobha Kapoor and Ekta Kapoor.
The film had its world premiere at the 67th BFI
London Film Festival on 14 October 2023.
It was theatrically released on 13 September 2024 to
generally positive reviews from critics.
It received five nominations at 70th Filmfare Awards including  Best
Film (Critics) and Best Actress (Critics) (Kapoor).
The film explores themes of mother, detective, grief, murder, murder mystery.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.